ILGWU. Gus Tyler papers, 5780/096
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II. Articles
  - "The Truth About Savings in America", 1990 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - "The Truth About the ILGWU" (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - "To Build a Liberal Coalition", 1967 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - "To Spend or to Save", 1989 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - "Unions and Politics in the United States", 1972 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Unions in Transition [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Unions in Transition [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - "The University and the Labor Union: Educating the Proletariat", 1979 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - "The Uses of History", 1973 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Vienna Revisited, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - "Walter Reuther", 1970 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - "The War of American Succession", 1964 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - "Warsaw Ghetto", 1989 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - "We Can Revitalize the Nation", 1992 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - "We're Pleading on Behalf of All Americans", 1977 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - "What Do the Young Need for Their Future Survival?", 1982 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - "What is a Liberal, Who is a Conservative?", 1976 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - "What, No Garment Rally?" (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - "What the Nixon Budget Means", 1973 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - "What to Do About Inflation", 1982 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - "Which Way Labor in the 80s", 1979 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - "Which Way the Working Man?", 1972 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - "The White Worker" (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - The World of the Blue Collar Worker and "White Worker, Blue Mood" (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - "Whither Labor on the Campus?" A Retrospective and Prospective Glance, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - "Who Shall Serve?", 1967 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - "Who's Turning Us into a Colony?" (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - "Why the Savings Rate is Low", 1990 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - "Why They Organize", 1972 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - "Women Tied to Low Pay in Occupational Ghettos", 1980 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Women, Work and Wages, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Work Ethic [folder 1 of 4], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Work Ethic [folder 2 of 4], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Work Ethic [folder 3 of 4], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Work Ethic [folder 4 of 4], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - "Work is Not a Four-Letter Word (I)", 1972 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - "The World of Work Gets Wider and Wilder" [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - "The World of Work Gets Wider and Wilder" [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Book Review. "Against the Evidence- The Becker Rosenthal Affair", 1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Book Review. "American Labor in Politics", 1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Book Review. "Strike Force" and "The American Mafia", 1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Book Review. "Beyond Equality-Labor and the Radical Republicans 1862-1872" (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Book Review. "Anchor Bible of Genesis", 1966 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Book Review. "Coalescing on the Left", 1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Book Review. "The Crime Confederation", 1971 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Book Review. "Days of Reckoning", 1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Book Review. "Dirty Politics", 1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Book Review. "Education in the United States", 1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Book Review. "The Evolution of the Volvo View", 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Book Reviews. "The Factory Girls" and "The Lowell Offering", 1978 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Book Review. "Gene McCarthy Twenty Years Later", 1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Book Review. "Guns and Garlic", 1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Book Review. "The Heyday of American Communism", 1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Book Review. "If I Had a Hammer", 1987 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Book Review. "Inside Job: The Looting of America's Savings and Loans" (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Book Review. "The Invention of the American Political Parties", 1967 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Book Review. "Jacksonian Aristocracy", 1967 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Book Review. "Labor Union Women Today", 1974 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Book Review. "The Man Who Plays Alone", 1970 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Book Review. "The Academy Eyes Organized Crime", 1974 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Book Review. "People versus Government", 1974 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Book Review. "A Percentage of the Take", 1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Book Review. "Perspectives on American Education", 1976 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Book Review. "A Political Life- The Education of John V. Lindsay", 1969 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Book Review. "Power and Greed: Inside the Teamsters Empire of Corruption", 1989 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Book Review. "President Reagan: The Role of a Lifetime", 1991 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Book Review. "Retrieving Democracy", 1985 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Book Review. "The Rise and Fall of Great Powers" [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Book Review. "The Rise and Fall of Great Powers" [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Book Review. "Senator Robert F. Wagner and the Rise of Urban Liberalism", 1968 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Book Review. "Sentenced to Life", 1974 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Book Review. "Strategy for Labor", 1967 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Book Review. "Toward a Democratic Left", 1968 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Book Review. "The Unions", 1972 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Book Review. "We Shall Be All: A History of the Industrial Workers of the World" (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Book Review. "Which Side Are You On?", 1991 (Box 21)
  - Book Review. "Work, Learning and the American Future", 1977 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Book Review. "Working", 1974 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Book Review. Miscellaneous, 1968-1972 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - AFL-CIO News Articles, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The American Federalist., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - The American Federalist., 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The American Federalist., 1969 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - The American Federalist., 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The American Federalist., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The American Federalist., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - The American Federalist., 1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The American Federalist., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The American Federalist., 1977 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The American Federalist., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Commentary., 1969 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Commentary., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Commentary., 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Dissent., 1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Dissent., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Dissent., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Dissent., 1974 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Dissent., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Dissent. "The Friedman Inventions" [folder 1 of 5], 1980 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Dissent. "The Friedman Inventions" [folder 2 of 5], 1980 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Dissent. "The Friedman Inventions" [folder 3 of 5], 1980 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Dissent. "The Friedman Inventions" [folder 4 of 5], 1980 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Dissent. "The Friedman Inventions" [folder 5 of 5], 1980 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Dissent., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Dissent. [folder 1 of 3], 1983 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Dissent. [folder 2 of 3], 1983 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Dissent. [folder 3 of 3], 1983 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Dissent., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Dissent., 1985 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Dissent., 1986 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Dissent. [folder 1 of 3], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Dissent. [folder 2 of 3], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Dissent. [folder 3 of 3], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Dissent., 1988 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Dissent., 1990 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Dissent., 1991 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Forward., 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Forward., 1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Forward. Anniversary Piece., 1987 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Forward. [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Forward. [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Forward. [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Forward. [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-January, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-February, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-March, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-April, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-May, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-June, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-July, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-August, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-September, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-October, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-November, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-December, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-January, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-February, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-March, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-April, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-July, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-August, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-September, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-October, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-November, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-December, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-January, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-February, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-March, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-April, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-May, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-June, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-July, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-August, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-September, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-October, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-November, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-December, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-January, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-February, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-March, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-April, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-May, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-June, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-July, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-August, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-September, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-October, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-November, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-December, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-January, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-February, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-March, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-April, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-May, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-June, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-July, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-August, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-September, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-October, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-November, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-December, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-January, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-February, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-March, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-April, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-May, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-June, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-July, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-August, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-September, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-October, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-November, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-December, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-January, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-February, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-March, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-April, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-May, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-June, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-July, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-August, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-September, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-October, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Tyler, Gus. Articles-November, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Tyler, Gus. Column for Liberal News, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Tyler, Gus. Article for Midstream, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - The New Leader. April Issues, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - The New Leader. January Issues, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - The New Leader. March Issues, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - The New Leader. April Issues, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - The New Leader. June Issues, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - The New Leader. February Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - The New Leader. March Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - The New Leader. April Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - The New Leader. May Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - The New Leader. June Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - The New Leader. July Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - The New Leader. August Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - The New Leader. September Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - The New Leader. Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - The New Leader. February Issues, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - The New Leader. May Issues, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - The New Leader. June Issues, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - The New Leader. July Issues, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - The New Leader. September Issues, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - The New Leader. Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - The New Leader. March Issues, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - The New Leader. April Issues, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - The New Leader. June Issues, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - The New Leader. July Issues, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - The New Leader. August Issues, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - The New Leader. September Issues, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - The New Leader. May Issues, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - The New Leader. December Issues, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - The New Leader. March Issues, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - The New Leader. Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - The New Leader. May Issues, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - The New Leader. December Issues, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - The New Leader. January Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - The New Leader. February Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - The New Leader. March Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - The New Leader. April Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - The New Leader. May Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - The New Leader. June Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - The New Leader. August Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - The New Leader. September Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - The New Leader. December Issues, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - The New Leader. Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - The New Leader. Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The New Leader. February Issues, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - The New Leader. May Issues, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The New Leader. June Issues, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - The New Leader. July Issues, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - The New Leader. August Issues, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - The New Leader. September Issues, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - The New Leader. December Issues, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - The New Leader. April Issues, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - The New Leader. April Issues, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - The New Leader. July Issues, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - The New Leader. January Issues, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - The New Leader. June Issues, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - The New Leader. July Issues, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - The New Leader. August Issues, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - The New Leader. September Issues, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - The New Leader. Pending Articles, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - The New Leader. March Issues, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - The New Leader. February Issues, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - The New Leader. December Issues, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - The New Leader. March Issues, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - The New Leader. May Issues, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - The New Leader. June Issues, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - The New Leader. July Issues, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - The New Leader. September Issues, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - The New Leader. October Issues, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - The New Leader. Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - The New Leader. December Issues, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - The New Leader. November Issues, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - The New Leader. February Issues, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - The New Leader. December Issues, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - New York Magazine., 1969 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - New York Magazine., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - New York Magazine., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - New York Magazine., 1972 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - New York Magazine., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - New York Magazine., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - New York Magazine., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - New Republic., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Ohio Teacher., 1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Union News. January-February, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Union News. March-April, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Union News. May-June, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Union News. July-August, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Union News. September-October, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Union News. November, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Series III. Speeches
  - Speeches, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Speeches. January, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Speeches. February, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Speeches. March, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Speeches. April, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Speeches. May, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Speeches. June, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Speeches. July, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Speeches. August 3-14, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Speeches. August 19-31, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Speeches. September, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Speeches. October, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Speeches. November 2-16, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Speeches. November 17-30, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Speeches. December 1-18, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Speeches. December 21-28, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Speeches. January 4-15, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Speeches. January 18-29, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Speeches. February 1-12, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Speeches. February 15-29, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Speeches. May 1-17, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Speeches. March 21-31, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Speeches. April 1-17, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Speeches. April 18-29, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Speeches. May 2-15, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Speeches. May 16-30, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Speeches. June 1-12, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Speeches. July 1-17, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Speeches. July 18-31, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Speeches. August 1-12, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Speeches. August 15-31, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Speeches. September, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Speeches. October 3-10, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Speeches. October 17-31, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Speeches. November 7-18, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Speeches. November 21- December 2, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Speeches. December 5-16, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Speeches. December 19-31, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Speeches. January 2-19, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Speeches. January 20-31, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Speeches. February, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Speeches. March [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Speeches. March [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Speeches. April, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Speeches. May [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Speeches. May [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Speeches. June [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Speeches. June [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Speeches. July, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Speeches. August [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Speeches. August [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Speeches. September [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Speeches. September [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Speeches. October [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Speeches. October [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Speeches. November, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Speeches. December, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Speeches. January, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Speeches. February, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Speeches. March, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Speeches. April, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Speeches. May, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Speeches. June, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Speeches. July, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Speeches. August, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Speeches. September, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Speeches. October, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Speeches. November, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Speeches. December, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Speeches. January, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Speeches. February, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Speeches. March, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Speeches. April, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Speeches. May, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Speeches. June, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Speeches. July, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Speeches. August, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Speeches. September, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Speeches. October, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Speeches. November, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Speeches. December, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Speeches. January, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Speeches. February, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Speeches. March, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Speeches. April, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Speeches. May, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Speeches. June, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Speeches. July, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Speeches. August, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Speeches. September, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 42)